{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Great Books",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "02 Handout 1",
    "LastModified": "19 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "02 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is the Arabic word for the Qur’an?",
      "answer": "Recitation",
      "choices": [
        "hung poems",
        "Magamat",
        "frame narrative",
        "Recitation"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How were the seven pre-Islamic poems dating to the 6th Century known?",
      "answer": "hung poems",
      "choices": [
        "Recitation",
        "Magamat",
        "frame narrative",
        "hung poems"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "These poems are also known as Al-Mu'allagat.",
      "answer": "hung poems",
      "choices": [
        "Recitation",
        "Magamat",
        "frame narrative",
        "hung poems"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the stories in rhymed prose related to the encounters of the witty Abul-Fath al-Iskanderi called?",
      "answer": "Magamat",
      "choices": [
        "Recitation",
        "hung poems",
        "frame narrative",
        "Magamat"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the other term of Magamat?",
      "answer": "assemblies",
      "choices": [
        "assemblies",
        "packages",
        "assets",
        "poets"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was the story of Bayad and Riyad written?",
      "answer": "Islamic Andalusia",
      "choices": [
        "Strait of Gibraltar",
        "Iberian Peninsula",
        "Nile River",
        "Islamic Andalusia"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "When was the Qur'an revealed to Muhammad by God, according to Islamic belief?",
      "answer": "610-632 BC",
      "choices": [
        "c. 900-1008",
        "8th Century",
        "13th Century",
        "610-632 BC"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "From what century onwards were distinctions made between al-fus 'ha and al-ammiyah?",
      "answer": "8th Century",
      "choices": [
        "c. 900-1008",
        "8th Century",
        "13th Century",
        "610-632 BC"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "When were the stories in rhymed prose related to the encounters of the witty Abul-Fath al-Iskanderi collected?",
      "answer": "c. 900-1008",
      "choices": [
        "c. 900-1008",
        "8th Century",
        "13th Century",
        "610-632 BC"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "When was the Story of Bayad and Riyad written?",
      "answer": "13th Century",
      "choices": [
        "c. 900-1008",
        "8th Century",
        "13th Century",
        "610-632 BC"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the narrative form of One Thousand and One Nights?",
      "answer": "frame narrative",
      "choices": [
        "short story",
        "folklore",
        "novel",
        "frame narrative"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who retold the stories of One Thousand and One Nights in Europe in the 18th Century?",
      "answer": "Antonine Galland",
      "choices": [
        "Jean-Andrei Lagrimas",
        "Reniel-Philippe Baldove",
        "Art Auguste Suñega",
        "Antonine Galland"
      ],
      "reference": "02 Handout 1",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}